## **Tolulope Adebesin**

Frontend Developer **GitHub:**https://github.com/Adebesin-Cell **Email:** adebesintolulope80@gmail.com **Phone:** +23490 600 58210

Lope.dev

SUMMARY

**CORE SKILLS** 

JavaScript (ES6+)

HTML/CSS/SCSS

Git/GitHub

React JS

Responsive design

**Firebase** 

Strapi

**Figma** 

Adobe XD

English

**LANGUAGE** 

Being a result-driven Front-end Engineer with over a year of experience in frontend development, software planning and intermediate knowledge of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap, Responsive design and design system, I am dedicated to creating and optimizing user-friendly web solutions and interactions for organizations to help them achieve their goals.

**PROJECTS** 

Links to my works can be found on **lope.dev/work** and more details can be provided on request.

**WORK EXPERIENCE** 

Zealarax Technologies - Frontend Developer Intern

December 2020 - November 2021

I worked as an intern at Zealarax Technologies and helped solve design challenges in the organization. I helped develop the frontend of the University of Abuja website, which can conveniently accommodate 1000 users. I also worked with the team in solving other real-world problems.

**Yett**i - Frontend Developer

November 2021 - Present

I worked as a Frontend Developer and helped in solving the problem of bridging the gap between the organization and their clients. I worked on the frontend of the software that solved this problem.

**EDUCATION** 

**Poly Staff College** - High School

August 2014 - November 2020

As a student a Ploy Staff College, I was the Head Boy in my final year, which helped me build my leadership skills. I was a member of the Maths Club and Computer Science Club, and, my involvement in these clubs helped me develop my tech skills.

Federal University of Technology, Akure - Computer Engineering,

Bachelor

September 2021 - Present

As a Computer Engineering student at the Federal University of Technology Akure, I am still in my first year and I am doing my very best to make the best use of my time at the University and end my journey here with good grades.